// JavaScript source code
var bank = [

    {
        question: "The calculation 63.444mm/20 = 3mm would be correct when significant figures are taken into account.",
        answer: "true"
    },

    {
        question: "pi = 3.141572",
        answer: "false"
    },


    {
        question: "When writing a range of dates, such as 1970 to 2017, the hyphen(-) is the technically correct choice, as opposed to the en dash(&ndash) and em dash(&mdash)",
        answer: "false"
    },

    {
        question: "New York State has a smaller population than Florida",
        answer: "true"
    },

    {
        question: "In anatomical terminology, is the thoracic spine considered to be inferior to the lumbar spine?",
        answer: "false"
    },

    {
        question: "'He should have swum that lap' is grammatically correct",
        answer: "true"
    },

    {
        question: "The large intestine is larger than the small intestine, in both diamter and length.",
        answer: "false"
    },

    {
        question: "Allen Iverson was selected 1st in the 1996 NBA Draft.",
        answer: "true"
    },

    {
        question: "Michael Phelps won 5 gold medals in the 2004 Summer Olympics",
        answer: "false"
    },

    {
        question: "Game Over",
        answer: "false"
    },


];
